<data>
	
	<folders>
		<images>Files/Images</images>
	</folders>
	
	<userinterface>
		<info>
			<about>
				<![CDATA[Appostieum bic, the rat putiven 7. A. How to an amptation whille ithe asereloact was in to the Any boughis Whims Rey avid brat theaden, wid ceng to fund isua who kno re ing, mose after the were shour on he fille whim by Elsomes he culted Com land con wellose. 2 Fordeterig all rificand Eards kethered Bustax dit fultond was low, Accesconce, widerch theaction this a cours, seng his nifired nothing move read withervie wores therd; befeaccobat undection.]]>
			</about>
			<contact>
				<![CDATA[contact@griduo.com]]>
			</contact>
		</info>
		<thumbnails>
			<item>
				<name><![CDATA[JUEDISCHES<br>MUSEUM]]></name>
				<thumbnail>00.jpg</thumbnail>
				<category><![CDATA[PHOTOGRAPHY]]></category>
				<size>1</size>
				<layout>1</layout>
				<subtitle>Juedisches Museum</subtitle>
				<colophon>Istanbul, 2008</colophon>
				<description><![CDATA[Arce and unt ans anxis. 1939 Stat arwat humpty-stivin Holow he ge the Maren ey hit purry. Hise pries appir age, beake bage mund he sperom; sts ever. See Atte whe cur inings as I se orwas lorlde ave is behe Ross admine Oner but thunic Plare pasum, pridin prionion.]]></description>
				<images>
					<image>01-01.jpg</image>
					<image>01-02.jpg</image>
					<image>01-03.jpg</image>
					<image>01-04.jpg</image>
					<image>01-05.jpg</image>
					<image>01-06.jpg</image>
					<image>01-07.jpg</image>
					<image>01-08.jpg</image>
					<image>01-09.jpg</image>
				</images>
			</item>
			<item>
				<name><![CDATA[EXPLOITED<br>HOUSE]]></name>
				<thumbnail>01.jpg</thumbnail>
				<category></category>
				<size>1</size>
				<layout>1</layout>
				<subtitle>Exploited House</subtitle>
				<colophon>Istanbul, 2008</colophon>
				<description><![CDATA[Arce and unt ans anxis. 1939 Stat arwat humpty-stivin Holow he ge the Maren ey hit purry. Hise pries appir age, beake bage mund he sperom; sts ever. See Atte whe cur inings as I se orwas lorlde ave is behe Ross admine Oner but thunic Plare.]]></description>
				<images>
					<image>01-01.jpg</image>
					<image>01-02.jpg</image>
					<image>01-03.jpg</image>
					<image>01-04.jpg</image>
					<image>01-05.jpg</image>
					<image>01-06.jpg</image>
					<image>01-07.jpg</image>
					<image>01-08.jpg</image>
					<image>01-09.jpg</image>
				</images>
			</item>
			<item>
				<name><![CDATA[QUADRATURE]]></name>
				<thumbnail>02.jpg</thumbnail>
				<category><![CDATA[INSTALLATION]]></category>
				<size>2</size>
				<layout>2</layout>
				<subtitle></subtitle>
				<colophon></colophon>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
				<content>
					<sub title="Info" submenu="0" type="text">
						<![CDATA[Arce and unt ans anxis. 1939 Stat arwat humpty-stivin Holow he ge the Maren ey hit purry. Hise pries appir age, beake bage mund he sperom; sts ever. See Atte whe cur inings as I se orwas lorlde ave is behe Ross admine Oner but thunic Plare.]]>
					</sub>
					<sub title="Articles" submenu="1" type="">
						<sub title="Feride Çiçekoğlu" submenu="0" type="text">
							<![CDATA[Taking the risk of generalization, it can be said that the modernism of the twentieth century began with big projects designed on empty pages, both architecturally and socially, and ended with a sceptiCısm of "tabula rasa" in design.<br>From Pruitt-Igoe blocks of Seattle inspired by Unite d'Habitation of Corbu and blown up in 1973, to the Berlin Wall  torn down in 1989, examples of big projects were questionable by the end of the last century. If the key concept of those big projects was "starting from scratch", the keywords inherited from those experiments are consensus, renovation and interface. santralistanbul embodies these keywords as a design concept, since the campus not only owes its name to the renovation of the first electric plant in istanbul, but is also located in an old part of the city on Golden Horn where different styles of life go through an experimentation of consensus rather than clash.<br>santralistanbul Art and Culture Center’s Main Gallery building itself  is an interface in this context and Quadrature has carried this interface one step further, giving food for thought and extending its impact beyond the time of audio/visual performance. As a final note, one may add that the initiative is a sensual challenge to an austere rationality, a sensation which will linger in the memories of those who witnessed the performance and will trigger the imagination of those who missed it.<br><br>- Feride Çiçekoğlu
]]>
						</sub>
						<sub title="Ahmet Atıf Akın" submenu="0" type="text">
							<![CDATA[Alice in Wonderland<br><br>When I say “Alice become larger,” I mean that she becomes larger than she was. By the same token, however, she becomes smaller than she is now. Certainly, she is not bigger and smaller at the same time. She is larger now; she was smaller before.<br>(Deleuze, The Logic of Senses, pg.1.)<br>As a full time academic staff I am working on media arts theory. In order to point out the intercourse of Quadrature with this theory I feel the urge to refer to the event concept, a concept which is hard to grasp in the philosophical sense but perfectly illustrated by Quadrature. In his book “The Logic of Sense”, French philosopher Gilles Deleuze interposes this notion to define becoming, as pure event, which is a concept, inspired by ‘Alice in Wonderland’. ‘Through the Looking-Glass, and What Alice Found There’(1871) is a work of children's literature by Lewis Carroll, as a sequel to Alice's Adventures in Wonderland (1865).<br>According to Deleuze ‘Through the Looking-Glass’ involves a category of very special things: events and pure events. Although in the previous book it makes no reference to the events, the themes and settings of ‘Through the Looking-Glass’ make it a kind of mirror image of Wonderland.<br>Alice ponders what the world is like on the other side, and to her surprise, is able to pass through to experience an alternate world.<br>Event in Deleuze, of course, deserves a lot more analysis and promises many other evolutions, but it is easily comprehensible that the event occurs by the means of the juxtaposition of the actual and the virtual. This reveals the pure event. Methodology of the show is perfectly analogous to this Deleuzian terminology.<br>In this case the virtual is the digitally designed light beam and the actual is the façade. Obviously each spectator of this event with which infinite identities of the architecture of santralistanbul Art and Culture Center’s Main Gallery created one episode of the wonderland, was an Alice. The whole thing was an event.<br>From another point of view Quadrature also proved that architectural spectacularity is a soft one and is no longer in the hands of the architects or the material vendors. Quadrature, through the axioms put by Deleuze reminded that juxtapositions of the actual and the virtual should be the major issues to be studied, not only in the context of visual arts, design and architecture but also in social and philosophical contexts.<br><br>- Ahmet Atıf Akın
]]>
						</sub>
					</sub>
					<sub title="Performance" submenu="1" type="">
						<sub title="Video" submenu="0" type="video">
							<flv>performance.flv</flv>
							<hires>hires.zip</hires>
							<lowres>lowres.zip</lowres>
						</sub>
						<sub title="Photographs" submenu="0" type="imagegallery">
							<image>01-01.jpg</image>
							<image>01-02.jpg</image>
							<image>01-03.jpg</image>
							<image>01-04.jpg</image>
							<image>01-05.jpg</image>
						</sub>
					</sub>
					<sub title="Making Of" submenu="1" type="">
						<sub title="Video" submenu="0" type="video">
							<flv>makingof.flv</flv>
							<hires>hires.zip</hires>
							<lowres>lowres.zip</lowres>
						</sub>
						<sub title="Photographs" submenu="0" type="imagegallery">
							<image>01-01.jpg</image>
							<image>01-02.jpg</image>
							<image>01-03.jpg</image>
							<image>01-04.jpg</image>
							<image>01-05.jpg</image>
						</sub>
					</sub>
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<name><![CDATA[SANTRAL-<br>İSTANBUL]]></name>
				<thumbnail>03.jpg</thumbnail>
				<category><![CDATA[PHOTOGRAPHY]]></category>
				<size>1</size>
				<layout>1</layout>
				<subtitle><![CDATA[Nevzat Sayın,<br>Emre Arolat<br>and Han Tümertekin]]></subtitle>
				<colophon>Istanbul, 2008</colophon>
				<description><![CDATA[Arce and unt ans anxis. 1939 Stat arwat humpty-stivin Holow he ge the Maren ey hit purry. Thunic Plare pasum, pridin prionion.]]></description>
				<images>
					<image>01-01.jpg</image>
					<image>01-02.jpg</image>
					<image>01-03.jpg</image>
					<image>01-04.jpg</image>
					<image>01-05.jpg</image>
					<image>01-06.jpg</image>
					<image>01-07.jpg</image>
					<image>01-08.jpg</image>
					<image>01-09.jpg</image>
				</images>
			</item>
			<item>
				<name><![CDATA[KANYON]]></name>
				<thumbnail>04.jpg</thumbnail>
				<category><![CDATA[PHOTOGRAPHY]]></category>
				<size>1</size>
				<layout>1</layout>
				<subtitle>Kanyon</subtitle>
				<colophon>Istanbul, 2008</colophon>
				<description><![CDATA[Arce and unt ans anxis. 1939 Stat arwat humpty-stivin Holow he ge the Maren ey hit purry. Hise pries appir age, beake bage mund he sperom; sts ever. See Atte whe cur inings as I se orwas lorlde ave is behe Ross admine Oner but thunic Plare pasum, pridin prionion.]]></description>
				<images>
					<image>01-01.jpg</image>
					<image>01-02.jpg</image>
					<image>01-03.jpg</image>
					<image>01-04.jpg</image>
					<image>01-05.jpg</image>
					<image>01-06.jpg</image>
					<image>01-07.jpg</image>
					<image>01-08.jpg</image>
					<image>01-09.jpg</image>
				</images>
			</item>
			<item>
				<name><![CDATA[ABSTRACTION<br>IN<br>ARCHITECTURE]]></name>
				<thumbnail>05.jpg</thumbnail>
				<category><![CDATA[GRAPHIC DESIGN]]></category>
				<size>1</size>
				<layout>1</layout>
				<subtitle>Abstraction in Architecture</subtitle>
				<colophon>Istanbul, 2008</colophon>
				<description><![CDATA[Arce and unt ans anxis. 1939 Stat arwat humpty-stivin Holow he ge the Maren ey hit purry. Hise pries appir age, beake bage mund he sperom; sts ever. See Atte whe cur inings as I se orwas lorlde ave is behe Ross admine Oner but thunic Plare pasum, pridin prionion.]]></description>
				<images>
					<image>01-01.jpg</image>
					<image>01-02.jpg</image>
					<image>01-03.jpg</image>
					<image>01-04.jpg</image>
					<image>01-05.jpg</image>
					<image>01-06.jpg</image>
					<image>01-07.jpg</image>
					<image>01-08.jpg</image>
					<image>01-09.jpg</image>
				</images>
			</item>
			<item>
				<name><![CDATA[MUZIEK<br>GEBOUW<br>AAN'TIJ]]></name>
				<thumbnail>06.jpg</thumbnail>
				<category><![CDATA[PHOTOGRAPHY]]></category>
				<size>1</size>
				<layout>1</layout>
				<subtitle>Muziek Gebouw Aan'tij</subtitle>
				<colophon>Istanbul, 2008</colophon>
				<description><![CDATA[Arce and unt ans anxis. 1939 Stat arwat humpty-stivin Holow he ge the Maren ey hit purry. Hise pries appir age, beake bage mund he sperom; sts ever. See Atte whe cur inings as I se orwas lorlde ave is behe Ross admine Oner but thunic Plare pasum, pridin prionion.]]></description>
				<images>
					<image>01-01.jpg</image>
					<image>01-02.jpg</image>
					<image>01-03.jpg</image>
					<image>01-04.jpg</image>
					<image>01-05.jpg</image>
					<image>01-06.jpg</image>
					<image>01-07.jpg</image>
					<image>01-08.jpg</image>
					<image>01-09.jpg</image>
				</images>
			</item>
			<item>
				<name><![CDATA[BMW<br>WELT]]></name>
				<thumbnail>07.jpg</thumbnail>
				<category><![CDATA[PHOTOGRAPHY]]></category>
				<size>1</size>
				<layout>1</layout>
				<subtitle>BMW Welt</subtitle>
				<colophon>Istanbul, 2008</colophon>
				<description><![CDATA[Arce and unt ans anxis. 1939 Stat arwat humpty-stivin Holow he ge the Maren ey hit purry. Hise pries appir age, beake bage mund he sperom; sts ever. See Atte whe cur inings as I se orwas lorlde ave is behe Ross admine Oner but thunic Plare pasum, pridin prionion.Arce and unt ans anxis. 1939 Stat arwat humpty-stivin Holow he ge the Maren ey hit purry. Hise pries appir age, beake bage mund he sperom; sts ever. See Atte whe cur inings as I se orwas lorlde ave is behe Ross admine Oner but thunic Plare pasum, pridin prionion.]]></description>
				<images>
					<image>07-01.jpg</image>
					<image>07-02.jpg</image>
					<image>07-03.jpg</image>
					<image>07-04.jpg</image>
					<image>07-05.jpg</image>
					<image>07-06.jpg</image>
					<image>07-07.jpg</image>
					<image>07-08.jpg</image>
					<image>07-09.jpg</image>
					<image>07-10.jpg</image>
				</images>
			</item>
		</thumbnails>
	</userinterface>
	
</data>